Jordan Wells

163 Oak Chase Lane Raleigh, NC 27604

T 919.906.7953

tjordanwells@gmail.com tjordanwells.github.io



https://github.com/ tjordanwells



https://www.linkedin.com/in/tjordanwells/

Profile

Full-Stack Developer interested in Data Visualization and intuitive design. I have an extensive background in

operations and am very much a self-starter and fast-learner. I pride myself on the ability to take point on projects as well as maintaining a dedicated focus. I am a creative problem-solver and leverage my experience from start-up environments to effectively deliver solutions.

Skills

Technical skills include: JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, React, Angular, HTML5, CSS, jQuery, RESTful APIs, Travis, Jenkins as well as MySQL and MongoDB.

Other: Project management, Agile, SCRUM, CI / CD

Experience

Full-Stack Developer / Support Engineer, Global Data Consortium; Raleigh, NC - 2019—Present

I am currently working to develop a streamlined support system application and escalation policy around the Worldview API service that Global Data Consortium offers. I am also working on in-house tools with the goal of creating a single-source-of-truth that helps enable all departments within the business utilizing Microsoft technologies.

Consultant, People's Coffee; Durham, NC - 2018

Consulted in the development and planning of opening a new coffee shop in Durham, NC through its entire life cycle. Responsibilities included overseeing buildout (on-site project management), brand development, marketing, as well as developing standard operating procedures and employee on-boarding.

Operations Lead, Slingshot Coffee; Raleigh, NC – 2016—2018

Responsible for all brewing related tasks, inventory management as well as R&D. I built a scalable system that allowed for the delivery of Target, Publix, as well as establishing Slingshot Coffee as a global brand within Whole Foods. I also increased brewing yields by twenty percent, leading to a higher profit margin.

Trainer / Management, Jubala Coffee; Raleigh, NC - 2014-2016

Prior to the opening of Jubala's second location, I developed and implemented a training platform that consisted of group sessions, as well as, one-on-one training sessions. After the on-boarding of the new staff, I moved into an interim General Management role for the first year of the new business.

Education

UNC-Chapel Hill – Full-Stack Development Certification, 2018 NC State University — English Literature, 2013–2016